# Nicho Rivera

Full-Stack Developer

# **Personal Info**

**Address** 

Salt Lake City, Utah

**Phone** 

831-244-0043

E-mail

nichoriverae@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/nicholas-rivera/

## Skills

Node/Express

React/Redux

Python/Django

Heroku

Docker

Git

Typescript

A Full-Stack developer with +1 years of development experience and +3 years of management experience in a professional setting. Using testing techniques, git version control, and a custom salesforce integration in daily workflow, I completed both individual and team based projects at the enterprise level.

# **Experience**

#### 2017-12 - Integration Manager and Software Engineer

2019-02

KNEW Health

- Architected and built crowd sourcing platform for medical expense sharing using React/Redux and Node/Express
- Built API endpoints using Node/Express, as well as an event driven messaging system for the backend
- Designed models for database
- Developed integrations and automations of third party services
- Designed email marketing and social media campaigns

#### 2017-08 - **Graduate Practicum - Marketing Analyst**

2017-12

New River Light and Power

 Developed automation program for social media in order to better inform consumers and drive customer loyalty

#### 2017-01 - **Graduate Assistant**

2017-01

Appalachian State University

- Implemented marketing material for study abroad programs through web, print, and social media
- Monitored analytics and SEO feedback to improved targeting and positioning of the program

## **Education**

2017-01 - Appalachian State University, Business, International Business, MBA

• 3.7 GPA

2008-05 - University of North Georgia, Spanish, French, B.A. 2013-05